talgov.com 2017-12-20

# Privacy Policy | Talgov.com

The following pertains to all pages within the Talgov.com domain:

Your privacy is important to us at Talgov.com. The purpose of this policy is to inform you about the types of information we gather when you visit our site and what we do with that information.

The following is a current list of information we may collect during your visit, or information that you provide to us voluntarily, and how we handle that information. This policy is not intended and should not be interpreted as a contract of any nature, either stated or implied. This document may change without notice, so please revisit this page often.

**Automatically collected information upon visiting talgov.com**  
In order to provide our visitors with a pleasant experience, our web servers collect some technical information automatically upon your visit. This includes your IP address, browser used, and date of visit. This information is collected to enhance our site by supplying us with statistics on web visits, and is only for internal use. No _**personally identifiable information** (name, address, email address, phone, etc.) _is collected automatically. The minimal information we do collect is kept confidential, and is used solely in summary form to enhance the services offered at Talgov.com, or to publish site usage statistics.

**Information you voluntarily supply to us**

  1. If you send an email to us with a question or comment, and that email contains personally identifying information, that information may be used to contact you in responding to your email, or may be forwarded to another agency for help in responding to you. This information will not be sold, rented, or voluntarily supplied to any agency, commercial or private, unless required by law.
  2. If you fill out an interactive form, the information you provide may be used to respond to your request, or may be forwarded to another agency for help in responding to you. This information will not be sold, rented, or voluntarily supplied to any agency, commercial or private, unless required by law.
  3. If you fill out a form that enables any type of service, the information you supply may be used in processing your request, and may be collected for inclusion in databases or directories, to be used for internal purposes only. This information will not be sold, rented, or voluntarily supplied to any agency, commercial or private, unless required by law.

**Email Addresses**  
Under Florida law, email addresses are public records. If you do not want your email address released in response to a public-records request, do not send electronic mail to this entity. Instead, contact this office by phone or in writing.

**Subscriptions**  
If you subscribe to any service on Talgov.com that involves continuous delivery of information to you, your contact information will be kept on a separate distribution list for each service until you submit a request to unsubscribe. This distribution list will be kept confidential, and will not be sold, rented, or voluntarily supplied to any agency, unless required by law.

If, at any time, you would like to unsubscribe from a distribution list, information on how to unsubscribe can be found at the end of the document sent to you.

**Photo Contest Submissions**  
By submitting a photo, an entrant (1) acknowledges that the photo becomes the property of the City; (2) authorizes the City to use the photo in its discretion without attribution or compensation; and (3) agrees to hold harmless, release and forever discharge the City from any and all claims, demands or damages arising out of or relating to entrant's photo submission. The City reserves the right not to accept, consider or post photos that do not meet requirements stated online.

**Cookies**  
Talgov.com does not set or use cookies.

Cookies are small files attached to some sites that track visitors and are accessed when revisiting the site that placed the cookie on your computer. They are used primarily for a more personal web experience, targeted advertising, and automatic completion of forms.

**Choice**  
You may decline participation in any activity that asks for information (i.e., surveys or emails). Your choice to not participate will have no effect on your ability to access information on Talgov.com. Most information provided via subscription can be found elsewhere on the site. If you don't want us to have any personally identifiable information, it is your choice not to give it to us.

**Online Payments  
** The use of third-party payment services, such as Western Union, Inc. or Active.com, may require you to enter your credit card information in a secure form. By using these sites, you are authorizing them to collect your account information to process your payment. Each site is secure and protects information you transmit to them using industry-standard encryption. These sites are only affiliated with the City of Tallahassee through payment handling, and this privacy policy does not necessarily apply to them.

**Mobile Applications / Mobile Devices / Mobile Payments**  
The City of Tallahassee provides mobile applications as a convenience for City of Tallahassee residents. City of Tallahassee is not responsible for any damages occurring as a result of the installation of, or use of, provided mobile applications. The City of Tallahassee is not responsible for support of your mobile device. 

Mobile applications may store information related to the functioning of the application on your device. Such information may include: user application preferences, utility account information, user id, email addresses. User private information such as passwords or debit account numbers, etc. will not be stored.

Any information transmitted from these applications uses industry-standard encryption. Information transmitted to the City of Tallahassee as a result of using these applications is likely to fall under Florida Sunshine Law.

Payments made from these applications make use of third-party payment services, such as Western Union, Inc. These sites are only affiliated with the City of Tallahassee through payment handling, and this privacy policy does not necessarily apply to them.

The City of Tallahassee is not responsible for the physical or electronic security of your mobile device. The City of Tallahassee is not responsible for any damages resulting from the physical or electronic loss of control of your device. 

**Refunds**  
Refunds are issued at the discretion of the City manager or the manager's designee, unless proscribed by specific language governed by the City's Code of Ordinances. Generally, refund requests should be made to the City department from which the service was provided. In your request, please include an explanation of your reasons for requesting a refund. Before enrolling for any services, please, make sure you have carefully read and understood the requirements. If you are not sure about a City-offered service, costs associated with the service, or have questions about activities or how the process is managed, please contact the City's Customer Service Center at (850) 891-0000 and you will be directed to the appropriate person.

**Florida Sunshine Law**  
As a general rule, Talgov.com does not disclose any personally identifiable information collected online except where you have given us permission, or where the information is requested to be disclosed and is public information under the State of Florida statutes or other applicable laws. Visitors to the site should be aware that Florida Statute 119 declares that all state, county, and municipal records shall be open for personal inspection by any person, and thus information collected by Talgov.com may be subject to examination and inspection upon request, if such information is a public record and not otherwise protected from disclosure by statute.

**Links to other sites**  
Talgov.com contains links to other sites. These sites follow their own privacy policy, and are not bound by this document. Any site outside of the Talgov.com domain is subject to its own guidelines, and should not be viewed as a part of the City's site.

**How to contact us**  
If you have questions regarding this privacy policy, feel free to contact us.
